{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"bd","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"logorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"žati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"cr","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tača","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"čov","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"te","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ca","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"litelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"telina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tinjstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"dol","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"dvos","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gluhon","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gluhosl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gn","osnova2":"zdo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"gor","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"grabl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gr","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"grobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"gus","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"in","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kasn","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kl","osnova2":"šta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kol","osnova2":"vka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"vstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"lica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"gati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ska","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pota","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"stve","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"šnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"šati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"mišl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"riti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sec","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"štaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"napr","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"can","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"catelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"čaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"lja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"nevr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"mački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"obav","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"siti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"oc","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"nuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ogr","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"om","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"oruž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"osm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ozl","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"nt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"smarica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ščanik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pob","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"podr","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"poned","osnova2":"ljak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prad","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"predsobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"stiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"štati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"laz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"nos","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"voz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"primor","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"tka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prizeml","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"priznan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"raskriž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"redosl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"č","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"dak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"rubl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sav","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"čanj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"cište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ćati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"kira","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"menka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"titi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ver","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"veroistok","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verozapad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"gović","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"spr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"stan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"stol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"susn","osnova2":"žica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tliti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tiljka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tionik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"šted","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"šut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"T","osnova2":"lovo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"rati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"stenina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"toplom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"tros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ugl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"uman","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"upotr","osnova2":"biti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vesel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vis","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"čnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ronauk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučitelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"šalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"štica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ština","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"tar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"trovit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"verica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vrt","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zal","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zapov","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zav","osnova2":"sa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zd","osnova2":"la","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"z","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zda","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"znica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"zo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"živ","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
